#### Contact

3058348280 (Mobile) rnadriel@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/adriel-rodriguez-a308a187 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Healthcare

Rehabilitation

**Wound Care** 

## Languages

Spanish

English

#### Certifications

**CMSRN** 

ONC - Orthopedic Certified Nurse

# Adriel Rodriguez

BSN, RN, CMSRN, ONC

Greater New York City Area

# Summary

Dedicated to the Nursing profession, committed to quality patient care, caring for ill, injured, disabled and convalescent residents/ patients by rendering general and specialized nursing care. Interact in a tactful, diplomatic and humanistic manner with patients, families, visitors and co-workers. Provide a safe, efficient and therapeutically effective caring environment, which insures the self-respect, personal dignity, rights and physical safety of each resident and guest.

Work effectively with patients, physicians, and health care professional involved in patient care to develop nursing care plans to fulfill patient's needs. Provide high quality patient care, remain calm and professional during critical incidents and adapt easily to environment and schedule changes.

## Work Experience:

- Doctors Hospital / Baptist Health South Florida, 9/2014 Present (RN, BSN)
- Hialeah Nursing and Rehabilitation Center, 7/2012 9/2014 (Risk Manager)
- Hialeah Nursing and Rehabilitation Center, 2010 7/2012 (LPN/RN)
- Home Health Services 2009-2012/ Hospice Nurse, 2009 2010 (LPN)

#### Other Skills

• Bilingual, can read, write, and speak Spanish / English fluently.

# Experience

Baptist Health South Florida

5 years 10 months

Patient Care Supervisor

January 2016 - Present (4 years 6 months)

BSN, RN

September 2014 - Present (5 years 10 months)

miami, florida

## Education

South University

Master of Science (MS), ARNP · (2014 - 2016)

Florida Institute for Health Care Risk Management Education LHCRM, LHCRM · (2013 - 2013)

Florida National University

Bachelor of Science (BS), BSN · (2012 - 2013)

Florida National College-Main Campus

Associate of Science (AS), Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2011 - 2012)

Keiser University-Ft Lauderdale

Licensed Practical Nurse, Nursing Education · (2008 - 2009)